

PRIYANKA THAKUR

Social Media Manager & Content Writer

My Contact

workpriyanka248@gmail.com



+91 7000924989



Indore

Hard Skill

- · Social Media Marketing
- Social Media Management
- Content Writing
- Copywriting
- Data Analytics

Soft Skill

- Observation
- **Decision making**
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Education Background

- Chameli Devi Public School Junior Secondary - 90% Completed in 2018
- Chameli Devi Public School Higher Secondary - 91% Completed in 2020
- Radiant Institute of Management **Bachelor of Commerce** All university 3rd ranker - 95%

Certifications

- **Digital Marketing**
- **Project Management**

About Me

Driven and successful Social Media Manager with an experience developing and executing campaigns that have driven significant traffic and generated leads, resulting in increase in followers and engagement, as well as increase in conversions across multiple platforms. Collaborated with cross-functional teams to develop visually compelling and engaging content, facilitate social media calendars and analyze metrics.

Professional Experience

Wrap Tales - Social Media Manager & Operations Head

May 2021-Present

- · Developed creative digital marketing strategies that increased social media presence and brand recognition.
- Expertly managed social media account, ensuring content was professional, engaging, and on-brand.
- Monitored analytics closely, providing detailed reporting and insights to inform upcoming initiatives.
- Optimized campaigns to ensure cost-effective use of resources.

Minime Bakers - Content Writer

September 2021 - August 2022

- · Maintained content trackers and created monthly reports for management.
- Created engaging captions for 100+ posts.
- Designed product labels and giftboxes.

Expand Grid - Social Media Manager & Content Writer

April 2022 - July 2023

- Created engaging posts for multiple social media accounts.
- Observed performance and identified trends
- Prepared reports on monthly performance and reported the insights.

Sugarboo Herbals - Content Writing Intern

September 2023 - October 2023

- Maintained content calendar.
- Created engaging captions.
- Published blog content.